https://sgmnow.com/terms-and-conditions-vod/

571-370-8400
support@sgmtraining.com
TERMS-CONDITIONS-DISCLAIMER
The SGM website (the “Site”) consists of various web pages owned and operated by Security Guard Management (“SGM”).  SGM is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein (the “Terms”). Your use of SGMtraining.com, sgmnow.com and all website pages constitutes your agreement to all such Terms. Please read these terms carefully, and keep a copy of them for your reference.  SGMtraining.com is an E-commerce Site providing more than 30 Online Security Officer Training Videos with tests.
INITIAL PROCEDURE
When you purchase the VOD program successfully, you will be granted immediate access to the training video library.  Within 24 business hours (excluding Saturday, Sunday and holidays), you will be mailed a customized link that you will be able to share with your employees to sign up for a free VOD membership under your account.  Do not share your personal login information with any employee, because your billing and credit card information will be able to be seen.  Only share with them the free link we send to you to distribute.  Using the free link will give them access to the training library, but they will not be able to see your billing or credit card information.  As long as your account remains valid, your employees’ access will remain active.  Employee sign up links are valid for thirty days.  At the end of thirty days if you wish them to continue, you will need to provide them with a new link (provided by SGM to you at no charge). VOD access is unlimited for all of your employees, up to 300 employees per month.  Each additional block of 300 employees is $99 per month (per each block of 300 monthly users).   SGM reserves the right to change as needed.  If any change is made, an advance notice will be sent to current active customers.
SGM CONTENT IS NOT FOR RESALE
Your use of the Site does not entitle you to make any unauthorized use of any protected content, and in particular you will not delete or alter any proprietary rights or attribution notices in any content. You will use protected content solely for your personal and internal company use only, and will make no other use of the content without the express written permission of SGM and the copyright owner. You agree that you do not acquire any ownership rights in any protected content. We do not grant you any licenses, express or implied, to the intellectual property of SGM or our licensors except as expressly authorized by these Terms.  The Video online (VOD) system is for your current employees and instructor use only.  You are not authorized to use this system for any pre-employment, marketing or sales without the express written permission of SGM and the copyright owner.  This SGM VOD video and exam system is not allowed to be a part of any online resale course(s), except by SGM only. An attempt to resell the SGM VOD system or videos will result in immediate termination of your account and will further result in a legal filing of theft and copyright infringement. By creating your VOD account, you hereby acknowledge and agree to these terms.
SUBSCRIPTIONS
Your VOD monthly subscription will be automatically billed to your credit card every thirty (30) days from the date of your order. Your subscription service will automatically continue monthly until you cancel.  When you cancel your account, the subscription will continue and terminate on the final day of the current paid billing period.   VOD sales and monthly subscriptions are final. No refunds. Failure of your credit card to renew will result in cancellation of your account.  Please contact us with any questions.
ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS
You or your active employees visiting the SGM website or sending emails to SGM constitutes electronic communications. You consent to receive electronic communications and you agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically, via email and on the Site, satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.
SGM does not knowingly collect, either online or offline, personal information from persons under the age of thirteen. If you are under 18, you may use SGMtraining.com only with permission of a parent or guardian.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES/THIRD PARTY SERVICES
SGMtraining.com and SGMNow.com may contain links to other websites (“Linked Sites”). The Linked Sites are not under the control of SGM and SGM is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. SGM is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by SGM of the site or any association with its operators. Certain services made available via the SGM website are delivered by third party sites and organizations. By using any product, service or functionality originating from the SGMtraining.com domain, SGM DOES NOT share such information and data with any third party with whom SGM has a contractual relationship to provide the requested product, service or functionality on behalf of SGMtraining.com users and customers.
NO UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED USE – INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
You are granted a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to access and use SGMtraining.com, sgmnow.com strictly in accordance with these terms of use. As a condition of your use of the Site, you warrant to SGM that you will not use the Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms. You may not use the Site in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Site or interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the Site. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the Site. All content included as part of the Service, such as text, graphics, logos, images, as well as the compilation thereof, and any software used on the Site, is the property of SGM or its suppliers and protected by copyright and other laws that protect intellectual property and proprietary rights. You agree to observe and abide by all copyright and other proprietary notices, legends or other restrictions contained in any such content and will not make any changes thereto.
You will not modify, publish, transmit, reverse engineer, participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit any of the content, in whole or in part, found anywhere on the Site.  The VOD video system is for use of your own current and active employees only.  You may not share access to the VOD system with any other company or entity.  You may not share access to the VOD system with any individual outside of your company.  You may not sell any type of subscription for access or to use this SGM VOD video program.  You understand and agree that SGM is the sole owner of this intellectual property and exams.  Failure to abide by any statements in these terms and conditions will result in immediate termination of your account and legal action filed against you.
INTERNATIONAL USERS
The Service is controlled, operated and administered by SGM from our offices within the USA. The SGM VOD video on demand, online video system is not for sale, access or use outside of the USA.  All sales are final.  Any use of any product or VOD online video system outside of the USA without the express written approval of SGM is strictly prohibited, and is cause for immediate termination of an account or purchase without refund.   If, with written express permission, you access the Service from a location outside the USA, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. You agree that you will not use the SGM Content accessed through SGMtraining.com in any country or in any manner prohibited by any applicable laws, restrictions or regulations.
INDEMNIFICATION
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless SGM, its officers, directors, employees, agents and third parties, for any losses, costs, liabilities and expenses (including reasonable attorney’s fees) relating to or arising out of your use of or inability to use the Site or services, any user postings made by you, your violation of any terms of this Agreement or your violation of any rights of a third party, or your violation of any applicable laws, rules or regulations. SGM reserves the right, at its own cost, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will fully cooperate with SGM in asserting any available defenses.
ARBITRATION
In the event the parties are not able to resolve any dispute between them arising out of or concerning these Terms and Conditions, or any provisions hereof, whether in contract, tort, or otherwise at law or in equity for damages or any other relief, then such dispute shall be resolved only by final and binding arbitration pursuant to the Federal Arbitration Act, conducted by a single neutral arbitrator and administered by the American Arbitration Association, or a similar arbitration service selected by the parties, in a location mutually agreed upon by the parties. The arbitrator’s award shall be final, and judgment may be entered upon it in any court having jurisdiction. In the event that any legal or equitable action, proceeding or arbitration arises out of or concerns these Terms and Conditions, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover its costs and reasonable attorney’s fees. The parties agree to arbitrate all disputes and claims in regards to these Terms and Conditions or any disputes arising as a result of these Terms and Conditions, whether directly or indirectly, including Tort claims that are a result of these Terms and Conditions. The parties agree that the Federal Arbitration Act governs the interpretation and enforcement of this provision. The entire dispute, including the scope and enforceability of this arbitration provision shall be determined by the Arbitrator. This arbitration provision shall survive the termination of these Terms and Conditions.
CLASS ACTION WAIVER
Any arbitration under these Terms and Conditions will take place on an individual basis; class arbitrations and class/representative/collective actions are not permitted. THE PARTIES AGREE THAT A PARTY MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN EACH INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PUTATIVE CLASS, COLLECTIVE AND/ OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING, SUCH AS IN THE FORM OF A PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION AGAINST THE OTHER. Further, unless both you and your employer agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person’s claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of representative or class proceeding.
LIABILITY DISCLAIMER
THE INFORMATION, VIDEOS, TESTS, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE SITE AT ANY TIME. SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED ON THE SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ALL SUCH INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND.
SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THIS INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SITE, WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR RELATED SERVICES, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SITE.
TERMINATION/ACCESS RESTRICTION
SGM reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to the Site and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice. To the maximum extent permitted by law, this agreement is governed by the laws of the State of Maryland and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Maryland in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of the Site. Use of the Site is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms, including, without limitation, this section. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and SGM as a result of this agreement or use of the Site. SGM’s performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in this agreement is in derogation of SGM’s right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the Site or information provided to or gathered by SGM with respect to such use. If any part of this agreement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the agreement shall continue in effect. Unless otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the user and SGM with respect to the Site and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and SGM with respect to the Site. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related documents be written in English.
ALL PRODUCTS AND SERVICES DISCLAIMER
By purchasing or using any of our products or services, you understand and agree that you may not copy, reproduce, distribute, publish, display, perform, modify, create any works, transmit, or in any way exploit any SGM content or product, nor may you distribute any part of this content over any network, including a local area network, the internet, sell or offer it for sale, or use such content to construct any kind of database. You may not alter or remove any copyright, SGM logo or SGM information or other notice from copies of the content on any SGM website. Under no circumstances is any license, permission, right or interest of any nature granted to anyone using this site, nor does any purchase of any of our products, or consumption of any service from us, imply that you are in any way entitled to such rights.  All of the contents of our products and website are protected from copying under U.S. and international copyright laws. Any unauthorized copying, alteration, distribution, transmission, performance, display or other use of this material is strictly prohibited.  Violation of any of these provisions is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. Violators may be subject to legal proceedings, to the maximum extent permitted by law.
DVD LIFE TIME WARRANTY
ALL SALES ARE FINAL. If within 30 days of your purchase a product is found to be defective, SGM will replace it, no questions asked.  Please call 571-370-8400 Monday through Friday, 9AM-5PM EST.  Upon approval SGM will send you a replacement product along with a prepaid return shipping label to return the defective item.  Failure to return the defective item within 30 days, you agree and authorize that SGM will charge the customer full price for the replacement item.   All products are protected with tamper proof sealing.
If an SGM DVD(s) malfunctions after 30 days of purchase, SGM will replace the defective DVD(s) for half the current retail price of the DVD, up to two years from date of purchase. The customer must call customer service at 571-370-8400 for an RMA number. Replacement orders cannot be done on the website. Customers must return defective DVDs to SGM within 30 days of replacement shipping date. If not returned, the customer understands, authorizes and agrees that SGM will charge the customer current full price for the replacement DVD plus postage and handling fees.
PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT
SGM may collect personally identifying information about individuals from forms filled out on this site. That information may be used for marketing and educational purposes, as well as provide relevant content to the user. Information is also collected in aggregate and used for internal reviews of what parts of the site user’s access or visit. This information is used to improve our Web site and to monitor overall traffic patterns.  Please be aware that Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information. The information practices of those links are not covered by this privacy policy. Users should also be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (such as user name or email address), that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.
In addition, cookies may be placed in the browser files of a user’s computer. These cookies are optional and may be refused any time using your Web browser software; however, doing so will make some parts of the site inaccessible. Please feel free to contact us if you have questions about this policy.
Consent to Use Personal Information/ Credit Card InformationSGM does not process any credit card transactions directly on its website. Online transactions are handled by a third party, which uses strict security measures to protect your credit card information. SGM does not disclose credit card account information provided by its customers. When customers choose to pay using their credit cards, SGM submits the information needed to obtain payment to the appropriate clearinghouse. SGM uses ConstantContact.com to distribute bulk e-mails with business tips and monthly specials. These e-mails are sent to those who sign-up for them on our website. SGM uses an online third party quiz system to host online exams for those who sign up for our Video on Demand service. Name and e-mail information is retained only for the purpose of identifying exam-takers and result notification. SGM’s website utilizes a number of plugins for various purposes such as security and to provide a better website experience. As part of its services, SGM may receive personal information such as e-mail address from companies that purchase training services on behalf of their employees and want each employee to have an individual login. SGM does not use this information in anyway other than for the purpose of identifying exam-takers and delivering results.
CookiesA cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web site’s computers and is automatically stored on your computer. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser for cookie settings.) Note that setting your browser to reject all cookies will make some parts of the SGM site inaccessible. SGM uses “Session Cookies” when logged into our sites which are needed with login and “Persistent Cookies” when using our sites to remember preferences like font size. SGM does NOT use third-party cookies that send information to other websites than those owned by SGM International.
Information SecurityWe work hard to protect SGM and our members from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular: we encrypt many of our services using SSL; we review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems; we restrict access to personal information to SGM employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.
For Legal ReasonsWe will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of SGM if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of SGM International, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.
ApplicationOur Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by SGM and its affiliates, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.  Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise through our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.
EnforcementWe regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made thecomplaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaintsregarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.
ChangesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).
TECHNICAL SUPPORT
SGM technical support is available Monday through Friday 9 AM Eastern standard Time until 5 PM Eastern Standard Time, excluding Saturdays, Sundays and Holidays:  support@sgmtraining.com.
CHANGES TO TERMS
SGM reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change the Terms under which SGMtraining.com is offered. The most current version of the Terms will supersede all previous versions. SGM encourages you to periodically review the Terms to stay informed of our updates.
CONTACT
SGM welcomes your questions or comments:
SGM
5500 Holmes Run Parkway
Suite 1217
Alexandria, Va. 22304
support@sgmtraining.com
Terms and Conditions
Agreement between user and SGMtraining.com
Welcome to SGMtraining.com. The Security Guard Management website (the "Site") is comprised of various web pages operated by Security Guard Management ("SGM").
SGM is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein (the "Terms"). Your use of
SGMtraining.com
constitutes your agreement to all such Terms. Please read these terms carefully, and keep a copy of them for your reference.
SGMtraining.com is a E-commerce Site providing 32 On-Line Security Officer Training Videos with tests..
Electronic Communications
You or your active employees visiting SGMtraining.com or sending emails to SGM constitutes electronic communications. You consent to receive electronic communications and you agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically, via email and on the Site, satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.
SGM does not knowingly collect, either online or offline, personal information from persons under the age of thirteen. If you are under 18, you may use SGMtraining.com only with permission of a parent or guardian.
Cancellation/Refund Policy
Any cancellation request made after 48 hours of service will not qualify for a refund. Please contact us at Tech@SGMtraining.com with any questions."
Links to third party sites/Third party services
SGMtraining.com may contain links to other websites ("Linked Sites"). The Linked Sites are not under the control of SGM and SGM is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. SGM is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by SGM of the site or any association with its operators. Certain services made available via SGMtraining.com are delivered by third party sites and organizations. By using any product, service or functionality originating from the SGMtraining.com domain, SGM DOES NOT share such information and data with any third party with whom SGM has a contractual relationship to provide the requested product, service or functionality on behalf of SGMtraining.com users and customers.
No unlawful or prohibited use/Intellectual Property
You are granted a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to access and use
SGMtraining.com strictly in accordance with these terms of use. As a condition of your use of the Site, you warrant to SGM that you will not use the Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms. You may not use the Site in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Site or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of the Site. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the Site. All content included as part of the Service, such as text, graphics, logos, images, as well as the compilation thereof, and any software used on the Site, is the property of SGM or its suppliers and protected by copyright and other laws that protect intellectual property and proprietary rights. You agree to observe and abide by all copyright and other proprietary notices, legends or other restrictions contained in any such content and will not make any changes thereto.
You will not modify, publish, transmit, reverse engineer, participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit any of the content, in whole or in part, found on the Site.
SGM CONTENT IS NOT FOR RESALE. Your use of the Site does not entitle you to make any unauthorized use of any protected content, and in particular you will not delete or alter any proprietary rights or attribution notices in any content. You will use protected content solely for your personal use, and will make no other use of the content without the express written permission of SGM and the copyright owner. You agree that you do not acquire any ownership rights in any protected content. We do not grant you any licenses, express or implied, to the intellectual property of SGM or our licensors except as expressly authorized by these Terms.
International Users
The Service is controlled, operated and administered by SGM from our offices within the USA. If you access the Service from a location outside the USA, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. You agree that you will not use the SGM Content accessed through SGMtraining.com in any country or in any manner prohibited by any applicable laws, restrictions or regulations.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless SGM, its officers, directors, employees, agents and third parties, for any losses, costs, liabilities and expenses (including reasonable attorney's fees) relating to or arising out of your use of or inability to use the Site or services, any user postings made by you, your violation of any terms of this Agreement or your violation of any rights of a third party, or your violation of any applicable laws, rules or regulations. SGM reserves the right, at its own cost, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will fully cooperate with SGM in asserting any available defenses.
ARBITRATION
In the event the parties are not able to resolve any dispute between them arising out of or
concerning these Terms and Conditions, or any provisions hereof, whether in contract, tort, or otherwise at law or in equity for damages or any other relief, then such dispute shall be resolved only by final and binding arbitration pursuant to the Federal Arbitration Act, conducted by a single neutral arbitrator and administered by the American Arbitration Association, or a similar arbitration service selected by the parties, in a location mutually agreed upon by the parties. The arbitrator’s award shall be final, and judgment may be entered upon it in any court having jurisdiction. In theevent that any legal or equitable action, proceeding or arbitration arises out of or concerns these
Terms and Conditions, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover its costs and reasonable attorney's fees. The parties agree to arbitrate all disputes and claims in regards to these Terms and Conditions or any disputes arising as a result of these Terms and Conditions, whether directly or indirectly, including Tort claims that are a result of these Terms and Conditions. The parties agree that the Federal Arbitration Act governs the interpretation and enforcement of this provision. The entire dispute, including the scope and enforceability of this arbitration provision shall be determined by the Arbitrator. This arbitration provision shall survive the termination of these Terms and Conditions.
Class Action Waiver
Any arbitration under these Terms and Conditions will take place on an individual basis; class arbitrations and class/representative/collective actions are not permitted. THE PARTIES AGREE THAT A PARTY MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN EACH'S INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PUTATIVE CLASS, COLLECTIVE AND/ OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING, SUCH AS IN THE FORM OF A PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION AGAINST THE OTHER. Further, unless both you and your employer agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person's claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of are presentative or class proceeding.
LIABILITY DISCLAIMER
THE INFORMATION, VIDEOs, TESTS, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS
SUPPLIERS MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE SITE AT ANY TIME. SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED ON THE SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ALL SUCH INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THIS INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SITE, WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR RELATED SERVICES, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF
THE SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF SECURITY GUARD MANAGEMENT OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SITE.
TERMINATION/ACCESS RESTRICTION
SGM reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to the Site and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice. To the maximum extent permitted by law, this agreement is governed by the laws of the State of Maryland and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Maryland in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of the Site. Use of the Site is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms, including, without limitation, this section. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and SGM as a result of this agreement or use of the Site. SGM's performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in this agreement is in derogation of SGM's right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the Site or information provided to or gathered by SGM with
respect to such use. If any part of this agreement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the agreement shall continue in effect. Unless otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the user and SGM with respect to the Site and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and SGM with respect to the Site. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related documents be written in English.
CHANGES TO TERMS
SGM reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change the Terms under which
SGMtraining.com is offered. The most current version of the Terms will supersede all previous versions. SGM encourages you to periodically review the Terms to stay informed of our updates.
Contact Us
SGM welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Terms:
